thulerv.com 2008-09-16

# Thule SMART RV

THULE takes user privacy seriously – we believe people should be able to contact us without fear of being tracked or overloaded with SPAM. Because we understand how important it is that you know what will happen to any personal information you give us, our mission is to adhere to policies that prevent unauthorized use of your personal information, to maintain the accuracy of the information provided, and to protect the privacy of your information. We have created this policy to explain how we collect data on our website and to educate users to what we are doing with this data. Our goal is to create the world’s best website for the world’s best rack system – and allow people to get information, browse and have fun on our site. 

**_What information does THULE collect and how is it used?_**  
**E-mail Request for Information** \- We use links throughout our site to provide you with the opportunity to contact us via e-mail to ask questions, request information and materials, or provide comments and suggestions. We may also request the opportunity to have one of our representatives contact you personally to provide additional information about our products or services. To do so, we may request additional personal information from you, such as your name and telephone number, to help us satisfy your request.

**Enrollment** \- If you choose to signup for our e-newsletter and special offers, we will request certain information from you. You may be asked to provide different personal information, such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, or credit card number. Other promotions may require different or supplemental information from you in order to apply.

In addition to the information we collect directly from you, we also gather information such as general usage of our Web site, viewing and traffic patterns, customer behavior and other similar information that is not specific to any one person. We use this compiled information, solely for the improvement of our Web site, our product and service offerings, our operations, and our customer service. 

**_Does THULE disclose the information it collects to outside parties?_**  
No! THULE does not resell any confidential customer information that is obtained or derived in its marketing efforts. However, we must cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer. 

**_Why do you need my email address?_**  
We may contact you by email to confirm enrollment or to check the accuracy of supplied information as well as to send you notices about special offers, new products, services, promotions and other similar information. Should you wish not to receive emails from us, please advise us by email. We will respect your wishes in regard to the methods we use to communicate with you. 

**_What are Cookies?_**  
"Cookies" are helpful pieces of information that a Web site places on your hard disk about you that make your return visits to the Web site more convenient. For example, THULE uses cookies to help identify you so that you may access your member benefits quickly and easily. We do not use cookies to collect personal information and we do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer for purposes that are unrelated to the Web site or your interaction with the Web site. 

**_How does THULE protect customer information?_**  
Our Web site is designed to protect your personal information. When you submit sensitive information via the Web site, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks you to enter sensitive information, such as credit card number, that information is encrypted and is protected with advanced encryption software known as “SSL”. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just “surfing”. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we take additional steps to protect your personal information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. 

**_Do these same policies apply to non-THULE Web sites that I access through THULE?_**  
We cannot be responsible for their privacy and security practices of non-THULE Web sites. You will notice that our Web sites may contain links to other sites such as our benefit providers. While we believe these sites share a similar commitment to consumer privacy and security, you should review that site’s privacy and security policies when linking to their site. 

**_How does THULE update its Privacy and Security Policy?_**  
Any changes to our Privacy and Security Policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it as well as the latest updates on how we maintain the secure portions of our Web sites. 

**By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of information as it is disclosed in this Privacy and Security Policy Statement.**

#### _Contact Information_

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
